{
    "id": "69c6d662096f499fbd7dc97632138605",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………… be there before 8 o’clock. (compulsion)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "would",
                "ought",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7467c49f72a43eda5e7c3bf9d39884b"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you lend me a few dollars? (polite request)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "72a02cbac410403b9622995313f5b509"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………. not have done this to me. (criticism)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "302ae11c1de24eab93de8129334c73ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………. be driving now. (probability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "would",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "182dbd7d657c42cba03c88536c516072"
        },
        {
            "question": "It …………………. rain in the evening. (weak possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "might",
                "can",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea33fa599ac84fd08d9f81d159b02bf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… not have waited for them. (lack of necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "can",
                "may",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6f6adb25126b4136b64c48613e5d1655"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I wait any longer? (necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Need",
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7fcd6d2dbe014bd7af9221b979711087"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… to follow traffic rules. (obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "ought",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81451553e43b4517a5626df033aacddd"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I turn the heating on? (necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Need",
                "Should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "13116da6cdcd4d09a72dcc5dc64542b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………….. have helped me. Why did you just sit and watch? (criticism)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9f126bd3d84e487f9eddf0d468c709dc"
        }
    ]
}